allenglandbadminton.com 2017-05-29

# Privacy Policy - Yonex All England Open Badminton Championships

## Cookies

To view information about cookies on this site, please visit the [cookie information page](http://www.allenglandbadminton.com/cookie-information/ "Cookie Information").

## Data protection and processing your personal information

If you give us personal information, such as your name, contact details and date of birth (for example to process an application or provide you with a subscription to a BADMINTON England related service) then this will be held and processed by BADMINTON England in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 (as amended from time to time).

BADMINTON England will need to transfer or give access your personal information to its County Badminton Associations, Affiliated Clubs, Tournament Organisers, agents or sub-contractors – who will process it strictly on BADMINTON England’s behalf. All of these agents and individuals have signed up to BADMINTON England’s Safeguarding information terms & conditions.

### Use of Your Personal Information

BADMINTON England may only use or disclose your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To perform the services you have requested (such as providing you with the benefits of BADMINTON England or providing you with information you have asked for) which may involve contacting you by post or e-mail.
  * To allow BADMINTON England to administer the game in England, for instance by organising tournaments.
  * To make parts of the website easier for you to use by, for example, not making you enter your personal information more than once.
  * The reasonable purposes of BADMINTON England, acting always within the Data Protection Act 1998 (as amended from time to time).
  * where BADMINTON England is legally required to do so, or where there is a public duty to disclose it
  * To market to you BADMINTON England and approved and appropriate third party products and services and other purposes as you may have consented to in submitting your personal data.

We may also use your information for detection of fraud and market research purposes.

### Sensitive Personal Information

Sometimes BADMINTON England will collect and process so-called sensitive personal data relating to you.

### Ethnicity Data

If collected from you, this will be used only to identify and keep under review equality of opportunity within BADMINTON England, and (anonymously) for statistical and reporting purposes.

### Disability Data

If collected from you, this will be used only to identify and keep under review equality of opportunity within BADMINTON England, and (anonymously) for statistical and reporting purposes.

### Criminal Records Data

BADMINTON England is registered with the Criminal Records Bureau to assist it in ensuring that those who take up appointments do not pose a risk to the children and vulnerable adults in its care. BADMINTON England will, therefore, process criminal records data disclosed by the CRB. This will be processed, handled and kept safe fully in accordance with the CRB’s Code of Practice for Registered Persons (a copy of which can be downloaded from <http://www.crb.homeoffice.gov.uk/>) and our own Policy Statement.

### Consent

By submitting your personal information to us, you signify your consent to our using the information provided in the manner described above. If we amend our privacy policy, it will be published on this web site. If at any time you wish to update the information which we hold about you, or if you wish to stop receiving information from BADMINTON England, please update your profile page on our website or notify [membership@badmintonengland.co.uk](mailto:membership@badmintonengland.co.uk).

Under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998, you may request a copy of the details we hold about you on our computer systems. BADMINTON England will charge a fee of £10 (or the current prescribed fee) for providing this information.

### Safeguarding Information: Terms and Conditions

##### **(A policy for associate bodies and partners of BADMINTON England)**

  * Individual / Member personal data will be distributed by BADMINTON England only to those who require the data for the purposes of associated organisation communication and/or tournament organisation
  * You must not distribute this data to any other persons without prior consent from BADMINTON England,
  * You have been CRB checked by BADMINTON England within the last 3 years
  * The data will only be used to contact players who have agreed to be contacted
  * The data supplied must not be used for mass marketing, or other commercial purposes where the individual member has opted out.
  * The data should be stored in a secure manner, such that it cannot be accessed by other people, including other users of your computer or system/network. It should be protected by a password if there are multiple users of the relevant computer or system/network.
